Bro made Chevette uncle
Ladies and gentlemen
I saw an ad and I'm looking for an address where Fernando's house is?
Nearby is a Chevette.
The car is stopped there.
I like to have a house and put it up for sale but it's okay if you put
it up for rent at this time when I'm stopped at home,
man the guy has an old car,
can rent me this car so I can make my deliveries.
Oh brother it's good for me it's good for Cara.
That's 1 negotiation issue.
It's called next to see you yourself in my responsibility
to rent so I can deliver here in the city.
It makes sense to you.
closed brother
I just broke my backpack,
man,
our trip is just like that.
Closed brother I'm already here at the gas station.
Already
Will this guy come?
bro
it's if someone comes along to sell them anyway,
I won't get in your way,
don't let me know,
then we're with the fuck.
Okay bro.
I thought how am I going to generate connection with people?
Man if I put 1 motoboy cool only mine is 1 delivery
you know it doesn't have 1 feeling.
I'm the face of my old brand.
And then if I deliver the Passenger directly to the person
I want an experience an approach connection.
Is it on?
I don't know if this idea will work out well but
my goal is to generate connection with people.
I hope I can get some sales done from now on because I need to pay for gas.
Ha ha ha and that's it guys.
I'll have a little tax.
A little bigger because of delivery but I hope to generate
bigger connection with people and result in sale.
Tamo together.
Do you want to drive outside and want me to fix your day?
I have twenty grams of happiness.
You're going to order there on my Instagram
and I'll take it to your house in person.
не т а а а и она вот та еит рото.